Moses.
I am
were dying of
people
My
and God told me
snakebite
a snake of
forge
to
it on
lift
bronze and
pole.
a
accident
were no
serpents
The
against God,
spoken
had
we
was the
venom
and the
earned.
our sin had
judgment
Him to take
begged
I
away.
the snakes
not.
would
He
to
me
told
Instead He
of the
image
forge the
us,
killing
very thing
it high.
lift
and
to
only
The bitten had
and live.
look
from the
now
I speak
of my life,
side
far
that came
light
by the
after
saw,
never
a night I
Teacher
called
when one they
seeker:
answered a
lifted up
Moses
And as
wilderness,
in the
the serpent
the Son
must
even so
up:
lifted
of man be
a
only
My bronze was
shadow.
on a
Jesus
They lifted
pole,
Roman
for us,
curse
made a
in our
our judgment
bearing
place.
me,
hear
So
are bitten
who
you
one of
every
that is
us.
was never in
cure
The
you;
sight,
plain
it hangs in
but
nothing
and costs you
look.
a
Jesus,
your eyes to
Lift
up for you.
lifted
Look,
live.
and